MELISSA WARD

UX/UI AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

mmacward99@gmail.com

wardmelissa.com

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

CSS & HTML

Figma

Github

Graphic Design

Version Control

EDUCATION

B.S. in Media, Arts, and Design

James Madison University

2018-2022

AWARDS

2022

Hashtag Sports Award Co-Nominee

PROFILE

Current Web Seasonal Associate with NFC Champions, the Philadelphia Eagles. A passionate UX/UI and Graphic Designer responsible for assisting with the design of in-app experiences, web pages, and CMS management. A dedicated team player who can adapt to any industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Associate

Philadelphia Eagles

2022-2023

- Co-led design on specialty campaigns for the Eagles' App and Website
- Designed website headers and graphics for a variety of digital marketing campaigns
- Collaborated with 5 other departments on 10+ projects
- Corresponded with editorial staff to develop 30+ app experiences generating over 600,000 total experiences launched
- Updated CMS weekly supporting 6 different marketing and corporate partnerships
- Built 50+ forms for Sweepstakes, Super Bowl, Suite Occupancy, Internal Operations, and more
- Led design in two of the top three highest viewed app experiences with 25,000+ views

Digital Intern

MidAtlantic Employers' Association

2021-2022

- Partnered with Managing Director to create MEA's current Power Point template for the Training & Development department
- Revamped and updated over 20 PowerPoint decks used for training delivery to audiences of 20 up to 200 participants
- Maintained strong communication 100% of the time throughout remote internship
- Received positive feedback from over 10 members/clients contributing to repeat business for MEA

Assistant manager

Jules Thin Crust

2015-2021

- Promoted from Server to Assistant Manager
- Managed shifts serving lunch and dinner to 20-30 customers
- Successfully resolved conflict resulting in customer satisfaction 100% of the time
- Warmly greeted new and returning customers while developing relationships which resulted in customer loyalty
- Memorized over 40 ingredients, 20 types of pies, and seasonal specials in order to give customized recommendations to guests
- Referred, welcomed and trained over 10 employees on various duties including point of sale operations, serving customers, opening and closing